<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BASH Scripting Guide on Meet Rajesh Gor</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/series/bash-scripting-guide/</link>
    <description>Recent content in BASH Scripting Guide on Meet Rajesh Gor</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 23:16:13 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/series/bash-scripting-guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BASH Scripting Guide - PART - 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bash-guide-p3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jul 2021 23:16:13 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bash-guide-p3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bash or shell won&amp;rsquo;t be much popular and powerful if they didn&amp;rsquo;t have some tools and utilities baked in. But even further they are supported natively in Bash, which just makes every task and challenge quite hassle-free to deal with. In this part of the series, I&amp;rsquo;ll try to cover an overview of some quite powerful and robust tools and utilities in Bash(shell in general) and also some of the advanced topics like dictionaries and positional parameters. Enough talk let&amp;rsquo;s dive in.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BASH Scripting Guide - PART - 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bash-guide-p2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 15:57:34 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bash-guide-p2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this part, topics such as switch cases, mathematical expression, arrays, and strings. This won&amp;rsquo;t be an in-depth guide to understand each and every concept, but to make users aware of the things and features in Bash. This also would not be an absolute basic guide, I expect to have some basic programming knowledge such as binary systems, logical and mathematical concepts. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, you won&amp;rsquo;t be bombarded with commands, I&amp;rsquo;ll just explain with easy examples to get started.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BASH Scripting Guide - PART - 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bash-guide-p1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 16:37:28 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bash-guide-p1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you are new to BASH and Linux, don&amp;rsquo;t you worry the community is the driving force here. If someone&amp;rsquo;s stuck somewhere, the platforms, forums, and blogs are ready to help anyone there. BASH is a short term of Bourne-Again Shell, it is a shell interface that has much more capabilities and functions than the simple Bourne shell(sh). It has some quite remarkable features and it is even capable of calling itself a programming language in some sense.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
